迈克 · 诺斯: 所以我们要创造一些看起来很熟悉的东西
&gt;&gt; Mike North: So we're going
to create some familiar looking
围绕字典类型构建的实用程序。
utilities built around a dictionary type.
这里有人在加薪时使用过地图和减薪吗？
Has anyone here used map and
reduce on raise?
举手表决。
Show of hands.
太棒了，各位。
Awesome, everybody.
所以我们要建立地图和缩减字典和
So we're gonna build map and
reduce for dictionaries and
我们要定义一个字典类型。
we're going to define a dictionary type.
这里有一个例子。
So here's an example.
我们在右边有一个文件扩展名字典
We have a file extensions
dictionary on the right
我们会说这是字符串数组的字典
we would say this is a dictionary
of string arrays, and
我们需要遍历这些值来讨论映射。
we want to iterate over the values for
talking about mapping.
我们希望生成具有相同键但具有转换值的字典。
We want to produce a dictionary with
the same keys but with transformed values.
所以我们可以得到像右下角这样的东西。
So we would get something like
what we see in the bottom right.
所以也许我们正在建立一个开放的文件对话，我们想要列出所有
So maybe we're building like a open
file dialogue where we wanna list all of
这些扩展看起来像图片
the extensions looks like jpegs and
Html 文件有多个有效的扩展名。
html files have multiple
extensions that are valid.
迈克 · 诺斯: 我们将利用我们的类型参数知识
&gt;&gt; Mike North: And we're going to use
our knowledge of type parameters so
这个应该和随意的字典一起工作。
that this should work neatly
with an arbitrary dictionary.
在那里我们可以操作那些我们没有的东西
Where we can operate on things
that have types that we don't
但是使用类型参数,
know the details about,
but using type parameters,
我们仍然可以抽象所有这些，操作这些数据结构，和
we can still abstract all of that away,
operate on these data structures, and
给我们的消费者回到高保真类型，然后他们可以继续和使用。
give our consumers back the high-fidelity
types that they can then carry on and use.
所以这是在挑战 / dict 文件夹
So this is in the challenges
slash dict folder